Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- A small female child sitting on the fence of a balcony in front of a house. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, 1957; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 6)
- A young couple standing looking off camera. Foto Kanarya. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Kanarya, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Couple; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- An older female in a black dress and a younger male standing next to a table with a flower decoration on it. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A young girl in a flower print dress and head scarf standing next to a covered pedestal. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A young couple in standing on an Oriental carpet in front of a dark curtain. Turkish writing on the front. 13.6 x 8.2 cm, 9 March 1944; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young couple, male in military uniform and female in a dark suit with square patterned collar. Studio Kenan. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Kenan Akgul, Uskudar, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Studio Photography
- Two females in light dresses with puffy updos. Seated female has a large black purse on her left arm. Ulus, Ankara, Turkey. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, July 1964; Studio Ulus, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Ankara, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young female with short wavy hair and a black dress with a large white flower in the cleavage. 13.5 x 8.2 cm, 8 June 1928; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
- A family group, older female and younger female are both wearing white dresses with the same patterned bow and tie on them. Studio Ridvan, Ankara, Turkey. 13.3 x 8.9 cm., Undated; Studio Foto Ridvan, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Ankara, Turkey; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A group of five males standing on grass with trees in the background. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young couple, female in a black dress with a five petal flower design, male in a light suit. 12.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A male wearing aviator sunglasses, seated next to a marina with boats flying Turkish flags in the background. 13.7 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Boats; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young girl in a white princess outfit and a young male in a prince outfit standing in front of some curtains with stars on them. 8.5 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Two older females seated in wooden chairs in satin dress with drinks in their hands. Turkish writing on the back, "Jockey Club". 13.8 x 9.2 cm, 1970; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
- A group of males and females at the beach in their bathing suits. Turkish writing on the back. Foto Fuat, Izmir, Turkey. 8.5 x 13.7 cm., Undated; Studio Foto Fuat, Izmir, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Bathing Suits; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- A young female in a dark fur coat with a dark brooch with flowers on her left chest. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Fur Garments; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Individual Portraits; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A young couple, possibily newly married, in between large flower arrangements. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Ceremony; Couple; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A family group, a seated older male with a suit and tie on surrounded by three standing females of varying ages. 13.3 x 8.5 cm, 26 January 1946; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
- A group of females of varying ages seated indoors with two young children standing in front of them in white dresses. 9.2 x 12.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Children; Family; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A male with dark rimmed glasses in a suit with two females, one in a dark dress, one in a light dress. 8.8 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Six siblings of varying ages, the youngest is seated on a flower patterend cushion. Foto Refik, Balikesir, Turkey. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Refik, Balikesir, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Balikesir, Turkey; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Studio Photography
- A young couple in their bathing suits standing on some rocks at the beach. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Bathing Suits; Beaches; Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A mixed group of males and females standing in a room with several large desks in it. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Offices; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A young female in a white dress with small flowers on it seated on a bench with her legs crossed. 13.6 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
- A group of young males and females in front of a building. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A male standing in a suit next to a light plant stand with a painted backdrop in the background. 13.8 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey
- A family group, one older female with four young children in front of her. Young female is wearing a light flower patterned dress with a large bow on her head. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
- A young female and a young male standing on a square tiled street with buildings in the background. 13.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Streets
- A bride standing with a seated covered female and a standing male in a dark suit. Same couple from ref728 and ref821. 8.7 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Couple; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Portraits
- A young male and young female in their bathing suits at the beach with umbrellas in the background. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Bathing Suits; Beaches; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young couple, female is wearing a dark skirt suit and holding a bouquet of flowers, male is holding female, dressed in dark suit. Foto Moda. 13.6 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Studio Photo Moda, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 9)
- A young female is wearing a watch on her left arm. Studio Gorcek. Same female in ref708. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Studio Gorcek, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Handtinting; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young female in a dark dress with a light lace collar. Overpainted lips in red. Studio Gorcek. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, 16 August 1959; Studio Gorcek, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young female in a dress with two light pom-poms on it, leaning aginst a wall. Foto Sabah, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Sabah, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A couple, female in a dark dress with a light lace collar and male in a dark suit. Foto Sabah, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.7 x 8.8 cm, 1955; Studio Foto Sabah, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Children; Coats; Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A female in dark coat, holding a dark purse and wearing a patterned scarf on her head. Foto Moda.13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Studio Photo Moda, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young male with a toothbrush mustache, in a dark suit and fedora. Turkish writing on the front. 13.4 x 8.5 cm, 4 March 1934; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A shirtless male wearing boxing gloves. 14.2 x 9.0 cm, 15 September 1978; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sports; Turkey
- An older male in a pin stripped suit with two females in dark dressed. Foto Sabah. 12.9 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Sabah, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young female in a light sweater with a stitched flower pattern on the left chest. 11.2 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
- A couple on their wedding day. Turkish writing on the front. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 14 July 1932; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils
- A mixed family group standing on the steps of the mausoleum of Mustafa Kemal Atatürk, Anitkabir, Turkey. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Anitkabir of Kemal Ataturk; Ankara, Turkey; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
- A family group, two females in dresses with squares on them holding a young baby and a male in a suit. Kültür, Izmir, Turkey. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Studio Kulturpark, Izmir, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A male in a pin stripped vest with three young females in dresses and coats standing in front a wall with a gate. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A family group, older male wearing a military uniform holding the hand of a young male similarly dressed. 13.9 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Children; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A young male in military uniform standing in front of some trees with a low stone wall in the background. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Trees; Turkey
- A family group, two older females with a young male in the middle and two small females seated on blocks in flowery dresses. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 10)
- A young couple on their wedding day. Bride is wearing a flower laced cloak overtop of her dress. Foto Yildiz, Antakya, Turkey. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Yildiz, Antakya, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Antakya, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils
- A group in formal dress and suits inside a house with a large chandelier. 12.8 x 8.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Ceremony
- A young male using an electric shaver standing next to a bunk bed. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A female holding a baby, both wearing white. Studio Sencek. 13.1 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Sencek, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A family group with a bride and groom standing in the middle of the group, outdoors. 8.5 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Family Portraits; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Portraits
- A family group, younger females are in dark dresses with light bows in their hair. Same couple from ref704 and ref821. 12.5 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Two older males and a younger male standing on the stairs of a building in front of a sign "T.C. Kartal Hükümet Tabipligi" (Office of a government doctor). 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Medicine; Men; Photographic Prints
- An older male with a beard seated on a chair holding a young baby with an older female and younger female standing next to them. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Photographic Prints; Students; Turkey
- A younger female seated on the lap of an older female in a coat with a fur collar and hat on a bench. 13.8 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Children; Family; Fur Garments; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A young child in a shiny double breasted outfit with legs crossed. Foto Sehir. 12.2 x 7.5 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Sehir, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A young female looking off camera in a black dress with a large white collar. 12.4 x 8.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Students; Turkey
- An older male in a dark suit wearing a fez. 14.0 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Fezes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Tarbouches; Turkey
- A young girl in a dark dress with a light collar and a bow in her hair. Foto Rekor. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, 16 February 1944; Studio Foto Rekor, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 12)
- A young male in a cap and gown with dark rimmed glasses, being kissed on the cheeck by an older woman in a polka dot dress. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Schools; Students; Turkey
- An older male and an older female both wearing glasses holding a young female between them with a vase of flowers in front of them. 8.6 x 13.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Children; Family Portraits; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Toys; Turkey
- A young male receiving a diploma on stage from another male, while a third male is holding a microphone. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Ceremony; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Schools; Students; Teachers; Turkey
- A group of males and one young female seated around a large table set for dinner. 9.0 x 12.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Drinking; Eating; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A group of five females, four in dark dress, one in a light dress standing in front of large flower arrangements. Foto Sabah, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Sabah, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A family group laughing and holding hands. Females are both in light silken flower dresses. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Ceremony
- A young couple seated on a large curved wooden bench. Studio Mustafa. 13.3 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Studio Mustafa, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Couple; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A portrait of an older woman in a dark dress with a light collar wearing drop earrings. Studio Mustafa. 13.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Studio Mustafa, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Portrait of a female with a paisley patterned scarf and hoop earrings. Studio Mustafa. 13.6 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Studio Mustafa, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 13)
- A family group, one young female with a large white bow in her hair and young female with an intricate flower head dress. Foto Park, Izmir, Turkey. 8.3 x 13.0 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Park, Izmir, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Children; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A couple, female has round dark framed glasses and male is wearing a dark jacket. Bursa, Turkey. 8.2 x 13.1 cm, 26 March 1940; Studio Yildiz, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Bursa, Turkey; Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A group of six females of varying ages. Studio Gorcek, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 8.4 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Studio Gorcek, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A horse drawn carriage in a park with people in it. 8.9 x 13.0 cm, July 1961; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Carriages & Coaches; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Parks; Photographic Prints
- A young couple in Western dress standing in front of a door with a large frosted glass window in it. 12.5 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Three young females in matching white skirts and shirts standing in the grass with large trees behind them. Foto Moda, Erdek, Turkey. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Moda Erdek, Balikesir, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Balikesir, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Parks; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
- A male playing an accordion with a group of young males and females standing nearby, while other children look on. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Children; Dancing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Schools; Teachers; Turkey
- An older female in a blonde wig standing in front of a metal fence with a body of water in the background. Cinarcik, Yalova, Turkey. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 19 May 1977; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Seas; Women; Yalova, Turkey
- Three young females in western dress standing in a large grass field. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A young male in a dark outfit holding a small black suitcase. 13.8 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkey; Uniforms
- A young female nurse sitting on a bed embracing a young female in a dress. 8.9 x 14.1 cm, 2 September 1963 Thursday; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Hospitals; Nurses; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- Three older females and an older male and a young male sitting a living room on a dark couch. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Children; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Five females seated on a low wall in front of a large building. 8.5 x 12.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- Three older males in suits and ties, holding glasses and cigarettes, standing in front a white paneled wall. 12.6 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Drinking; Gatherings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Turkey
- A young Turkish male in bell bottom pants, sitting in front of a body of water with large boats on it. Sirkeci Pier, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.9 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Bosphorous; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints
- Two young males in the same suit with similar sashes and hats. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Boys; Circumcisions; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Six women in white lab coats standing on a road outside with trees and buildings in the background. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Medicine; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Uniforms; Women
- An older couple seated on chairs next to a young male lying in bed. 8.7 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Boys; Circumcisions; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Two young women in Western dress leaning on a tree in front of a small stone wall. Mardin Amerikan Koleji (American High school). 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mardin, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Women
- A couple seated on an ornate sofa with a young male making a grimacing face. Foto Sait, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey. 8.8 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Sait, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Children; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
- A family group, possible bride in the middle in the back row standing in front of a large flower arrangement. 8.3 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Portraits
- Large group of males and one female standing in front of a single story building with an awning over the front door. 8.8 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Agriculture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Nevsehir, Turkey; Photographic Prints
- A young couple standing a crowded room next to a man in military uniform. The female is wearing a short white silk dress with a jacket. 8.8 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Turkey; Uniforms; Wedding Ceremony
- A light haired woman in an elaborate dress, looking off camera. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A group of young children standing on stone steps, one is holding a football. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, 1934; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Children; Flags; Footballs; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A family group gathered around a seated bride and groom. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils
- A family group standing around a bride and groom in front some flower arrangements. 9.1 x 13.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Portraits
- An older female sitting on an armchair with a small child on her lap. 8.4 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Children; Family Portraits; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Turkey; Women
- Young females in school uniform, seated around a large wooden table with bookcases in the background. 8.2 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Books; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Libraries; Photographic Prints; Schools; Students; Teachers; Turkey
- Women in white coats seated and standing in front of a white stone building. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Arts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Students; Teachers; Turkey; Uniforms